[music]
Hello,
>> questions.
Uh, start with center. You guys lost
Kingsley, obviously. Where does that
leave you in the position for this week?
>> Um, yeah. Well, Graham is feeling a lot
better.
>> Yep.
>> Kingsley, how I mean, you guys started
him two games in a row. Um, how how did
you guys get away? Uh well, he liked the
opportunity, you know, so he felt like
that was the right thing for him. And
man, I wish him well. Love Kingsley,
man. He's a good dude, man. Worked his
tail off. Uh has here for a couple of
years and so wish him the best of luck,
man.
>> Was he someone you wanted on the 53?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Like Kingsley, you know,
he's done a good job. He's really, you
know, he's grown.
We talked a lot about the offensive line
this year, but when you have the the
number of tight ends missing that you
guys have had, how did that kind of
impact your offense down the stretch?
Not having Sam, not having Brock.
>> Uh yeah, it's um tight ends are a big
part of what we do. You know, they uh
certainly the run game um but the pass
game as well. So when you you know, when
you lose your your you know, your top
two guys, it it uh becomes a little
harder for sure. So uh that's it's
affected us. Um, now that being said,
it's good to get Zilster back. You know,
he's a pro, he's a vet, uh, can do a lot
of jobs and and then FK, you know, as
well. Ferg's, uh, you know, he he's, uh,
he's got some versatility, too. So,
that's it's been good to have those two
guys.
>> Just one more on on Kingsley and more
bigger picture logistics of of practice
squad coaching. Um, you know, when a
team express interest or you express
interest in a guy on another team's
practice squad, um, is it kind of like a
handshake, first right of a refusal
thing? Like you said he liked the
opportunity, but like did you have
>> Well, I think what it is is it's we're
not going to we're not going to lie to
anybody, you know, like I can't I can't
guarantee a starting spot, you know.
We're not going to do that. I I can't
guarantee that. So, um they guaranteed
it and so it's all good.
You know, it's good for him, man.
>> What do you What do you hope Jir Gibbs
takes from this season? I mean, at his
best, you saw what he'd been able to do.
you know, one of the most electrifying
guys in the league, but then some of
these losses has been like major
difference in his numbers. What do you
what do you hope he takes from from this
season, especially here in this last
game?
>> Well, he's like any other player. you
know, he's not done growing and
developing and uh [snorts] you know, um
and so I I think so much of it is um you
know, you you always got to look to
yourself and uh you know, what are the
little things, the little details that
you can improve on personally um that
can help maybe some of these runs or or
you know, and then and then you work off
of that, you know. And so just always
hone in on the little things, your first
step, your landmarks, your and um and
I've said this all along, man. If we can
just get he or David to bust one of
these early, you know, if we can just
get a breakout run early, it goes a long
way. It really does, man. Uh and we just
haven't been able to do that. Um but
man, he look, he works. He grinds. Uh
both of those backs do. So uh it we just
we haven't been able to do it in a
while. You know, we hadn't been able to
break out of there. But um but he's not
done growing. That's what you love about
Gibbs, man. He's got so much room to
grow in both areas, run and pass. And I
feel like that's where he's really
blossomed is in the pass game. And
there's so much left to to work with
here.
>> Asked about the tight ends. We haven't
asked about Leaporta in a minute. How is
he recovering? How'd that go? What's his
long-term outlook, I guess, with
>> Yeah. Uh he's, you know, he's he's
getting better. um you know it wouldn't
be um you know it wouldn't have been one
of those things where you know you get
in the playoffs did he have a chance to
play? No, it wouldn't be that. But but I
feel like uh you know next year that
that certainly isn't off the table early
in the year. You know, you'd like to
believe training camp will get him, but
you're talking about a back um and he's
improving but yet he's not completely
healed.
>> Do you sort of longterm? I mean you said
maybe training camp. So, what sort of
long-term I don't know, questions are
there about his his future now?
>> Well, I think it's anytime you you start
talking about a neck or a back or um you
know, some of those things depending on
a knee, what kind of knee it is or what
it looks like, you know, those can be
concerning just cuz you don't know you
you don't know exactly what's going to
come out of that. You know, uh how do
they recover? Um, so that's always going
to kind of be back there a little bit uh
until
either he is fully healed or he's not
quite there, but I'd like to believe
he's got, you know, he'll have a lot of
time to heal here. You know, he's
rehabbing every day. Certainly feels
better after the surgery than he did
right before. So that's a that's a
positive, right? You know, uh took a lot
of stress off that nerve. So, you know,
we'll see.
>> We know what Decker's gone through this
year with the shoulder. obviously an
illness last week. I mean, just is that
someone you have to think about playing
this weekend just based on what he's
gone through to get to this point?
>> Uh, yeah. I mean, I the plan is to get
Decker going. You know, he wants to
play. I mean, he wanted to play last
week, but he was, um, he looked like he
was, you know, about 6 in from the
grave. So, um, you know, it was
unfortunate, but, um, but, you know,
barring anything this week, uh, he's
he'll be ready to go. I think um you
know it's it's talked a lot about with
players like sometimes disappointment
can fuel growth um helping them reach
that that next level. It's obviously
been a disappointing season. Didn't
didn't reach the goal. How does how does
that apply to the coaching staff and
maybe you Dan? I mean you've seen so
much. You've gone through highs and lows
as a player and as a coach like
>> how does this maybe this season fuel you
going forward?
>> Well I think that's exactly what it
does. You know, I think that's exactly
what it does. Um,
you know, it uh and sometimes you got to
hit rock bottom before you can work your
way back up. And relative to where we
were at, this is rock bottom, you know.
Um, but as bad as it looks, I said this
the other day, it's not as far away as
it may be appear. Um, we just got to get
a few things back in line here. Um, but
it does apply to the coaches, you know,
and no different than the players.
That's what you look for. I do for as a
head coach, man. How do other coaches
respond uh to what we're going through
here? We got one more, you know, and
what are we willing to do uh to try to
get this win?
>> Seasons before where you didn't make the
playoffs, I'm assuming. Um disappointing
2122. How did you kind of pick yourself
up and and use that fuel to to make
yourself a better coach, have a better
team the following years? How how did
you get out of those? Well, I mean it
it's look, failure for me, failure is
easy to it it it it's very good
motivation. You either go two ways,
right? I mean, you either just go down
in the dumps and you sit in a dirty
diaper for a while, you guys got kids,
and you just lay there. You just sit
there, right? And it's miserable. Or you
change your diaper and you get the hell
up and and uh and you go and um and so
the motivation is is respect, man. You
know, you don't want to go through what
you went through again. um you know and
you'll do whatever it takes um to not
let it happen again. Whatever it takes
and or you'll die trying relative to
what we go through in this league.
>> How much did you get a sense of you know
when you took over as play caller kind
of all the things that Jared had to deal
with I guess this these last you know
nine weeks especially
>> I'm sorry a little bit louder. And when
you took over as play caller, I mean,
how much did you get even better sense
of what Jared had to deal with with the
with, you know, the loss of Sam and, you
know, the the turmoil within the
offensive line and everything else and
just, you know, what he had to kind of
weather um over these last nine weeks.
Well, you anytime, you know, to to
really bo to be in that that position
with him, you um you know, you you
really you know, you learn a lot about
each other. And we've known a lot about
each other. It's not the first time
we've done this, but but you do. And and
I do know this the every time you lose
somebody, more pressure gets applied to
him. Every time you lose somebody, more
pressure gets applied to him. man,
right, wrong or indifferent, uh I put
more on him, you know, and that I put
more on him and uh and it can become,
you know, it can become hard, man. Now,
um he he'll never he'll always embrace
all of it, you know, give me every bit
of it. I can handle it. I can give it to
these guy. I can do. [snorts] And so,
but it does we put a lot on the guy, you
know, and uh
you know, and it's why I respect him.
One of many reasons why I respect him. I
mean, he's played at a high level and uh
he really hasn't had everything at his
disposal. We just kind of, you know, you
know, you lose a player here or there
and you lose him in different areas, but
he's handled it like a champ.
>> So, over the course of the season, what
what did you like about play calling and
what were the challenges that
>> I'm not going to get into all that right
now. That's not the time. If you want to
ask me next week, then I'll tell you I'm
not going to get into that until the
week after or whatever, but you know.
>> Okay. Thanks, Hey, hey, hey. [music]
[music]
>> [music]